-
Speaker 1: What should happen to the people responsible for this?
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): I think they should be punished. Like, there should be some type of, like, punishment towards them for bringing children to a show like that, especially
Woman 3: without parental consent or even just any information at the school board, even. Not even consent from the students attending. Like, there was, I mean, there were some students who were
Speaker 4 (higher-pitched voice): very upset. There was children who had cried. There was some religious students who were very,
Speaker 4 (higher-pitched voice): - Disturbed. - Very disturbed.
Speaker 5: This broadcast is not suitable for children under 18. Viewer discretion is advised.
Speaker 6: Tell
us all
Speaker 6: about this amazing production. Okay, Little Red Warrior and His Lawyer is a wild ride of a show. If the permission slips
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): that went home to Saskatchewan parents for an end-of-year field trip were accurate, they would have said, "Do you give your permission for your child to attend a production that contains subject matter not appropriate for public consumption?"
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): scenes depicting explicit, sexually graphic content, glorification of violence, promotion of hatred against an identifiable group, explicitly sexualized themes including simulations of intercourse, straddling, fisting, dry humping, grinding, extramarital affairs, threesomes, pregnancy as a result of that threesome, cuck holding,
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): foot-worship, bondage and dominance, erotic dancing, nymphomania and fetishism, pregnancy degradation and implied physical child abuse of an infant, objectification of women, including white women, female lawyers, Premier Danielle Smith and Queen Elizabeth II as deviant sexual objects, glorification of binge-drinking, roofing, psychedelics,
and
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): anti-development, anti-oil, and anti-Western culture sentiments. While the corrupt, lazy, mainstream media sold Little Red Warrior and his lawyer at the Globe Theatre as a "trickster fable" to the public, and Regina Public Schools and the Globe Theatre blame each other while simultaneously claiming to have done nothing wrong, now Rebel News is pleased to tell the other side of the story.
Speaker 8: It's a fun show. It will leave you laughing, gasping, and talking a lot after you
leave. It's my pleasure
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): to introduce you to five of the most bright, thoughtful, and engaged young people from Saskatchewan. They're a good sampling of the some 400 students from 14 classrooms who were exposed without their nor their parents' consent or knowledge to the Drag Queen field trip. Although they're all 18, to safeguard their dignity and privacy,
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): something Regina Public Schools couldn't manage, and because of the sensitivity of the subject matter, Rebel News has obscured their identities. What they and 395 of their Saskatchewan classmates did was extraordinary. They turned what was supposed to be an innocent field trip into an international media event.
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): 400 brand-new, baby, independent journalists were born the day of that field trip, and that's something to be proud of. What they reveal is everything. Not only do they lay waste to the official statements offered by Regina Public Schools in the Globe Theatre to the corrupt mainstream media, but they add much-needed context to the ten-second Drag Queen video we all saw last
week.
They
Speaker 7 (higher-pitched voice): were intelligent, intuitive, and thoughtful beyond their years, describing the field trip, the play, Little Red Warrior and His Lawyer, and the worldwide attention as they experienced it. So without further ado, meet the future
Speaker 9: of Saskatchewan.
Hello,
Woman 10: students of Canva Collegiate in Regina, Saskatchewan.
Hi. How old are you
Woman 10: and what grade are you in? I'm
Speaker 11: 18.
Speaker 12: I'm in grade 12.
Speaker 12: I'm also 18. I'm on grade 12. I'm
Speaker 13: also 18 and I'm grade 12.
I'm
Speaker 12: also 18 and grade 12.
Speaker 13: I'm also 18 and grade 12.
Speaker 14: Saskatchewan's best.
Woman 10: Okay. This is our future. Okay, kids. Tell me what your teacher told you before you went on this field trip. What, how did they sell this to you? What did they say? Um, well,
Speaker 15: she said it's going to be a little spicy, but nothing too crazy.
Speaker 15: Yeah, there's, like, a couple mature moments is all they told us.
Speaker 11: Yeah, that's what they were told, too. Like, last semester, we also went on one, and it was very
Speaker 16: nice. It was called... It was a Christmas Carol, and we expected nothing like this. Yeah, it was like the Scrooge. We expected nothing like this, and neither did the teachers.
Okay, so
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): they were surprised as well.
Speaker 16: Yeah, they were surprised. They were absolutely
Speaker 18: surprised.
But
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): they told you it was spicy, so they...
Speaker 18: Oh, that's what they were told. They were
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): mature themes, but nothing like...
Speaker 20: No nudity or anything like that was expected.
They
Speaker 16: only said there would be a couple like slightly mature scenes. They never really said how bad it would get. And it was pretty
Woman 3: bad. It was pretty bad. That's the globe. Like the globe said that it wouldn't be anything like too bad. Like it was just going to be like a couple mature moments. Even at the beginning of the show, like a woman came out to talk and like...
Woman 3: introduce it kind of to everybody it was like a couple mature moments like never said i just
Speaker 22: everyone was like completely on the website it also said it was uh 14 plus mature
Speaker 27: themes that's all they told the teachers the teachers had no idea that it was like anything worse than that that's the only reason we went
they
Speaker 28: also changed it to only 16 plus i think it should be 18 really
Speaker 29: like this isn't this is adult content that you guys saw
Speaker 30: yeah yeah for sure for sure
Speaker 30: Like,
Speaker 14: if this was a movie in the theaters, people under 18 wouldn't be able to
Speaker 30: go. Exactly, no.
Speaker 14: So you don't think the kids that are younger than you should be exposed to what you guys were exposed
Speaker 31: to? No, no, no, no, no, no. There were grade nines there, and they shouldn't have been seeing that.
Speaker 32: 14-year-olds that drove in from Yorkton two hours to go watch this play. Yorkton! Yeah.
Speaker 33: Yorkton we need to have a word well Yorkton
Speaker 34: didn't know either they had no idea because they brought grade nines they were told that it was 14 plus
Speaker 23: they basically every school got like the same like description it's not too much they said it
Speaker 36: fell under the curriculum uh
Speaker 28: curriculum with the satirical theme but i didn't see any any satire in it like it was just really bad they
Woman 3: also believed that it would like suit the curriculum because it kind of was supposed to focus on like indigenous and like claiming the land
Woman 3: back but i feel like it really lost the plot and it was kind of just all about sex was basically what the
Speaker 37: whole really yeah yeah like like
Woman 3: the scenes about like there were
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): scenes about him trying to take his land back but they were very short where the hell did the drag queen come in
Speaker 38: like she was queen elizabeth she
Speaker 39: was queen elizabeth it was pretending to be
Speaker 40: yeah
Speaker 39: stop i'm gonna die queen elizabeth is portrayed by a drag queen
Woman 3: yeah
Speaker 41: stripper drag queen
Woman 3: stripper on a pole yeah so how it happened was there was like two moving like kind of half staircases almost that like came in from both ends and met in the middle yep uh and then the drag queen walked out in barely any clothes and just like kind of jammed
Speaker 20: a pole into the ground and just like started stripping in front of all the kids.
Speaker 32: - Yeah, the scene was in a courtroom
Speaker 32: room and the indigenous guy summoned summoned the queen to help him win the case and the queen did some diabolical things to
the
Speaker 42: judge terrible terrible terrible i don't know
Speaker 22: if there was consent involved but it was definitely not yeah if you like it was pretty
good
Speaker 44: okay
Woman 10: so do you guys tell so you guys so you guys so your parents signed the permission slips you all that all the parents paid the dollars to go for you guys to go to the club theater you guys get there on a bus or how'd you get
Woman 46: there like a
Woman 10: school bus
Woman 46: yeah yeah okay okay and how many kids were in that or how many people were in the theater and it
Speaker 47: was it was
every scene yeah
Speaker 47: Every school was student. There was four different schools there. There was like Southfield C, Yorkton, there was Scott. Tom was there or Scott. CRP, I think. Yes, CRP was there. What's CRP?
Speaker 51: Campus
Speaker 50: Regina. Yeah,
Speaker 11: I think, yeah. There was a lot of schools that paid to go and had no idea that this was going to happen. And they
Speaker 52: hold two student matinees a year.
and
Speaker 52: they chose a christmas carol for one and then they chose this
Speaker 23: and so the crazy part is that elsa was showing like a month ago and like frozen right and they didn't bring us to that
Speaker 53: and so they chose this as
Speaker 54: their matinee instead that's an interesting
Speaker 53: choice isn't it it's almost like it was intentional like yeah it's almost like it was intentional
Woman 10: that they wanted to expose you to this what are your parents saying about this like where what like what has happened because if i was a
Woman 10: I have six kids. I have four kids in Regina Public Schools. I have a daughter that graduated from this high school. My godmother was amongst the first graduating classmates of this high school. They're going nuts. What are your parents saying?
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): Well, my dad was kind of like, wow.
Woman 56: Like, there's no reason to parade that in front of all these kids. Like, that's not what we paid for. Like, we better get a refund type thing.
Woman 3: Like, he was pretty, like, shocked. Um...
But
Woman 3: I know for a lot of other people that it was, like, way more than just shocked.
Speaker 21 (higher-pitched voice): Yeah, I mean, we're old enough to the point where our parents are like, oh, that's really weird. Why would they choose that?
But I know a
Speaker 21 (higher-pitched voice): lot of, like, the younger kids, like the grade nines, their parents are pretty upset. Yeah.
Our
Speaker 16: parents were, like, they were more, like, fortunate that our teachers chose the professional route to get us out of there as quickly as possible. Yeah, we left
early. Very early. We
Speaker 53: need to talk about the teacher's response.
So
Speaker 58 (higher-pitched voice): some teachers, and I'm going to say the teachers that walk those students out
of
Speaker 58 (higher-pitched voice): that performance space are
Woman 46: Saskatchewan's best teachers. What did your teacher say to you? Like, what happened? Tell me, tell us all what happened.
She
Speaker 59: just, like, really apologized for, like, what we saw. She said she had no idea that whatever we saw was going to be in the play. She literally had absolutely no idea.
Speaker 60: also addressed what was going to happen with the
Globe and
Speaker 60: how the Globe reacted and, like, where it was all
Speaker 61: going. What did she say was happening? The Globe is supposed to give out a statement
Speaker 52: and...
Speaker 52: apparently they changed it to 16 plus and yeah and like
some of
Speaker 52: their
Speaker 62: sponsors are pulling out after this as well oh do you do you want to know who sponsors the globe theater
Woman 46: the government of canada the government of saskatchewan the city of regina ralco radio tourism saskatchewan the list goes on and on you know who sponsored the show
Woman 46: you're telling me that the show was being mean to a judge right that was part of the act but
Woman 3: like they were doing some weird things with the judge for the act like like unconsensual like just are we allowed to describe what
Speaker 64: happened yes uh so i don't know i
Speaker 65: don't know if we can no you can you honestly go
Speaker 59: ahead okay so it's your it was your experience they kind of use uh like the queen yeah the queen literally used like the force she reached out her hand
Speaker 59: almost like she's grabbing his balls and literally
Speaker 66: just, like, squeeze. And, like, squeeze like this. And the guy was, like,
Speaker 69: wincing, like,
Speaker 67: literally like that. There was another part where she goes, like, this and starts going, like, this. And then he, like, pretends that it's, like,
Speaker 71: going up his, like, butthole. In his butt, yeah. And he's, like, he's, like, in pain, pretending to be, like, in pain and hurting, and then she just, like, takes it out. So this
Speaker 44: is part of the act. And this is, this is a, this is the Queen Elizabeth character played by
Speaker 58 (higher-pitched voice): a drag queen doing...
Speaker 58 (higher-pitched voice): these sort of graphically sexual, suggestive things with their, like, actions against a character that's a judge. Yes. Would it surprise you to know that MLT Aitken's, one of Canada's most prestigious law firms, sponsored that entire performance?
Speaker 73: Wow. That's kind of shocking. Yeah, that's pretty shocking.
Woman 10: What do you have to say to the leadership of MLT Aitken's? Like, do you support them supporting this performance?
I
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): think they should reconsider who like they're supporting
with their
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): If you're
Speaker 75: a law firm, like, there's a big loss of professionalism there. And they
Speaker 76: were back putting down the judges in the play too, they were kind of portraying them as lazy, like throughout the whole thing the judges were portrayed as lazy and like not helping.
Speaker 22: The judge chose the other person's side because the lawyer was like, the lawyer
Woman 56: was flirting with the judge. And it was a woman, yeah. The woman was flirty and sexy and so like they kind of like portrayed it as the judge being
Speaker 77: like- Corrupt.
Woman 56: Corrupt.
Woman 56: Like choosing the sexy lawyer to win because she's dancing around and like spreading her legs for him. I was portraying her as like a drag queen
Speaker 78: that came out and started stripping in the court. So I don't know. In front of underage
Speaker 79: people that gave her money. A little kid gave her a $20 bill, which she put in her bra. And she like took it from his head and threw
Speaker 81: her mouth. A grade nine had like a $20 bill.
Speaker 81: I'm going to need to sit. I'm not
Speaker 71: joking, guys. She leaned over the barrier towards one of the row of grade 9 students and one of them handed her 20. No, they
Speaker 82: were grade 12s. I went to school with them. Were they? Yeah, they were grade 12s. They were grade 12s. Students. Still high school students.
Speaker 71: Like, put it in her mouth or something and then she, like, goes back to the pool, strips around a bit and, like, is, like, stuffing it in her...
Not
Speaker 71: even like really a shirt
Speaker 83: Was this like was the
Speaker 84: performer a man or a woman do you guys know a man dressed as a
Speaker 85: woman with Fake very realistic breasts. Yeah,
Speaker 86: no, they weren't very realistic.
Speaker 85: They were pretty realistic Where they
Speaker 88: were realistic where the point where there was details that didn't
Speaker 22: need to be there. Yeah,
I
Speaker 22: and like the globe also they they said that they messed up but they didn't really give a reason on why they chose
it
Speaker 89: like they don't why they chose no one has a reason
Speaker 90: but they're just saying like yeah we messed up and
they just
Speaker 52: gave like the refund and stuff and they changed it to 16 plus now they have to give a statement with like and like we haven't heard back from them it was horrible to watch for like anyone young and like none of us expected to see a whole porno as a play on a Let's go with Trapp.
It
Speaker 92: was,
Speaker 93 (lower-pitched voice): um...
Not a
Speaker 93 (lower-pitched voice): lot of the plot made sense. Everything was kind of just thrown together. The stripper didn't need to be there. It would have been fine without that.
Speaker 94: Yeah, the whole thing kind of just got lost. They said there was only a
couple moments
Speaker 94: of maturity, but honestly, the whole thing, just from the start, was okay. But right after the
Speaker 76: start,
it was
Speaker 76: just, like, basically the whole thing turned sexual. Basically, immediately. It's, like, right after we've met the first female character is when everything started turning sexual.
And
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): just back to, like, the being disrespectful towards the judges and stuff. I mean, like, at the
beginning of
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): the play...
Woman 56: red deserves to get a slap on the wrist because he um had like attacked a uh construction worker and so he's
Woman 3: gonna get a slap on the wrist from the judge but what actually happens is in this courtroom the judge takes off his robes and under under
it is
Woman 3: like lingerie like bondage and he has like one of those like kinky sexy whips gives like a little slap on the wrist to little
Woman 56: red - I'm a warrior. - Yeah.
Speaker 95: Like all the lights are red. Like it just turns. - Set it turns.
Speaker 95: And everything just kind of turned for the worse. It was very, like...
Speaker 96: It went sideways. Yeah.
Speaker 95: Yeah. Do
you
Speaker 97: guys hear what these kids are telling us?
Speaker 98: And this is all true. Like, this is all true. And there's videos going around on the internet about it. What
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): should happen to the people responsible for this? I think they should be punished. Like, there should be some type
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): of, like...
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): punishment towards
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): them for bringing
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): children to a show
Woman 3: like that, especially without parental consent or even just any information. Not even consent from the students attending. Like, like there was, I mean, there was some students who
Speaker 4 (higher-pitched voice): were very upset. There was children who had cried. There was some religious students who were very
upset.
Speaker 4 (higher-pitched voice): very disturbed yeah there was
Speaker 28: like the teacher from yorkton was like shaking
Speaker 99: and like she had told our teacher like our teacher was like are you okay and she's like no i brought grade nines like i didn't know this was happening and she was like she was like so scared for her
Speaker 100: job even this has put people's jobs at risk like their families and stuff and they just weren't told at all so it's just yeah and
i
Speaker 101 (higher-pitched voice): mean like the teachers themselves are the ones who are getting kind of
a
Speaker 101 (higher-pitched voice): like in trouble for it
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): from the parents like they're the ones kind of facing the punishment right now because all these parents are angry but it wasn't even the teacher's fault to begin with like it really like the teachers did handle it really well in my opinion like right away like like they left early they were like this is not okay they all were very apologetic um and just genuinely like sorry and even like asking is is everyone okay or like if anyone needs to have a
We can
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): have a private discussion. Oh, wait, wait, I'm sorry. Wait, just
Speaker 58 (higher-pitched voice): pause right there. So you're telling me that the same institution that walked you into that highly inappropriate and confusing subject matter is saying, do you want to talk about it with us for their offering to help you through this?
Well, I
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): think that some people were a little bit like bothered by what happened. And I think that...
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): The teachers were offering their support. If you're not okay, if this really harmed you, you're allowed to come to us and
tell us
Speaker 2 (higher-pitched voice): this, and we can find a way to move forward. Do you think that we should trust the people
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): that were responsible for doing this, though? But I just don't think it was the teachers at all. Fair enough. You know what? I saw a teacher walk out. I saw a teacher walk out on one of your videos that you sent. That's the best teacher in Saskatchewan, okay?
Woman 3: They were angry. They were very angry at the Globe, and they did everything they could.
Woman 3: like even requesting a script ahead of time so they could read through the script and you like verify that this was something that was safe for their students to watch and the globe never sent it so it really is because of the globe i think is at fault
Speaker 28: here the teachers like didn't waste any time to get this out to the globe
Speaker 16: like as soon as we left the
uh the
Speaker 103: globe theater like the bus just came back quickly and we hopped on the bus as soon as we got back to the school
Speaker 99: i'm pretty sure like all the teachers called the globe like to get like
Speaker 99: Like, what the hell is going on? Why would you do this? You
could get
Speaker 99: an explanation. Exactly, yeah. The
Speaker 104: Globe just didn't have an explanation. All they said was, like, we messed up.
Yeah,
Speaker 105: we're meeting with our lawyers. We'll make a statement. If you want
Speaker 106: to have a meeting with them. They're lawyers. Like, the same one sponsoring the show are
Speaker 95: different ones, you think? Oh, my gosh. Probably different. Some of the schools didn't have their buses because they were out
Speaker 107: of town. So some
Speaker 95: of them had to wait until the end.
Speaker 95: right and so the raw students
Speaker 107: were forced to see the whole thing yeah even if you leave
Speaker 108: like the theater
Speaker 107: there's
Speaker 109: still a tv in like the lobby showing what's happening so even if you leave the theater in the round you're still subject to what's happening in the theater on the screen just
Speaker 90: in front of like like the theater and then right in front of the lobby like before you go downstairs to leave like in front of the tv there's just a tv and there's like four angles
Speaker 110: of just
Speaker 110: what's going on inside. So you can, some kids were still watching and laughing.
They
Speaker 111: were finding it hilarious. - Sorry, we're
Speaker 110: going to spoil it. - It
Speaker 112: ends up in a threesome. - Between Little Red Warrior, his lawyer, and his wife.
Speaker 113: - What?
Speaker 114: -
Oh my
Speaker 114: God. - Sorry to spoil it. - That's what we heard anyway, from the Greenall students.
Woman 10: - People are watching this all over the internet, and this is what they think we do in Saskatchewan.
Is
Woman 10: this who we are in Saskatchewan? This
Speaker 115: is not who we are. I don't think
Speaker 19 (higher-pitched voice): anybody here supports that other than people who
Speaker 116: created it themselves. I think we're being portrayed really badly for this because it's all over already, but nobody had a clue other than the Globe Theatre. Nobody knew this was going to happen. And this is not what we do.
Speaker 52: Yeah, we did not want to watch that. And I don't think this was on any of us.
None
Speaker 118: of us wanted to be here. We don't do this in
Speaker 52: Saskatchewan. No.
We
Speaker 118: don't support...
Speaker 118: We don't support those actions, especially in front of children or anything like
that.
Speaker 93 (lower-pitched voice): Yeah, I want to make it clear that it really depends on how it was portrayed. I think that people can watch whatever they want to, but willingly. We
Speaker 119 (lower-pitched voice): were not told what we were going to go see,
so it
Speaker 119 (lower-pitched voice): was completely disrespectful, and
a lot
Speaker 119 (lower-pitched voice): of people were exposed to something they didn't want to see. It
Speaker 27: was shocking. None of the students, none of the teachers. I don't think it was any of us. I think it was really just the globe.
Speaker 21 (higher-pitched voice): Didn't tell anybody kind of tricked people into going even though it wasn't appropriate for our age group It's not what we usually do in Saskatchewan. Isn't like that like boundaries
Speaker 120: were being crossed That should never be crossed just like with children, especially if you have
a
Speaker 17 (higher-pitched voice): message for premier Scott Moe Who's maybe the only guy in the whole world that can fix this? What would you suggest he does?
At least put
Speaker 121: that rating to 18
plus
Speaker 12: Like an
Speaker 119 (lower-pitched voice): outside person who reviews
like
Speaker 119 (lower-pitched voice): plays that are going to be presented to minors just
Speaker 101 (higher-pitched voice): to make sure this doesn't happen again like have somebody from like an outs like a third person view making sure that these things
Woman 3: are actually safe for our schools and children to be i also
Speaker 122: think the globe should pay us they're pretty rich
look at
Speaker 123: like 35 million bucks that's what i'm saying
Speaker 88: how many sponsors you have give us like more than a refund i need some money some people
Speaker 124: went in grade nine and didn't want We need some
Speaker 126: compensation for what we saw.
Speaker 124: Compensation? Yes,
Speaker 126: compensation.
Speaker 126: it
Speaker 127: was pretty it was pretty insane i just i think that there should be being more done to make sure this like kind of incident doesn't happen again yeah
Speaker 21 (higher-pitched voice): i think that everyone deserves an apology that went and had no idea and i think the globe does deserve to be punished for what they chose to willingly choose children without their knowledge so
Speaker 55 (higher-pitched voice): And, like, also, just, like, while we're at it, like, we
Speaker 118: took time out of our day to go there and watch a play and then didn't even get to fully watch a play. Like, I think something should be done about that. We got gyps of a field
Speaker 128: trip.
Speaker 129: Yes. It's the only 12th year. Field trip of the year. And then we had to leave early and it was actually terrible. So it was really awkward. I feel like there should be more
Speaker 118: being done to be made up to the children who had to go see that.
Speaker 118: than just being like oh well you have your money refund for your ticket like like that's not really enough like you kind of just showed a whole bunch of grade 12s like and grade nines like naked pole dancing and boobs and shaking breasts in people's faces this was
Speaker 132: just horrible on her name yeah i don't know what liz did to deserve this
i
Speaker 134: can't tell you how proud i am of you for having this conversation it takes immense bravery this is a really touchy
Speaker 136: topic.
Speaker 136: um like i said though i i really want to hear from all your moms um you tell your teachers and you tell everybody inside that school that rebel news wants to hear from them okay that we just want to get to the bottom of what happened and make sure that the saskatchewan student population um has access to the best you guys didn't have that yesterday and it's clear that that's not what happened to you this week excuse me earlier this week um but uh i just adore you guys and i'm really really proud of you and what you've done so well done kids thank
Speaker 137: you so much yeah from the queen city for rebel news i'm lee smart